We will begin this exercise with the 3 -to -1 method.
Find a comfortable position.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath. And while exhaling, mentally repeat and
visualize the number 3, three times.
To help you relax physically at level 3, I'm going to direct
your attention to different parts of your body.
Relax your scalp.
Relax your forehead.
Relax your eyes and the tissue surrounding your eyes.
give yourself a slight smile and relax the muscles of your face
relax your throat
Relax your shoulders, arms and hands. hands.
Take a deep breath and while exhaling relax your chest
externally and internally.
Take another deep breath, and while exhaling, mentally relax
your abdominal area, externally and internally.
Relax your thighs.
Relax your knees. knees.
Relax your calves.
Relax your feet.
you are now at a deeper healthier level of mind deeper than
before this is your physical relaxation level three whenever you
mentally repeat and visualize the number three your body will
relax as completely as you are now and more so so every
time you practice.
To enter mental relaxation level 2,
take a deep breath and while exhaling,
mentally repeat and visualize the number 2 three times and you
are at level 2,
a deeper level than 3.
Level 2 is for mental relaxation where noises will not distract
you instead noises will help you to relax mentally more and more
to improve mental relaxation at level 2 practice visualizing
tranquil and passive scenes do that Now, take another deep
breath and while exhaling, mentally repeat and visualize number
one three three times.
You are now at level one, a deeper, healthier level of mind.
to help you enter a deeper healthier level of mind I'm going
to count from ten to one on each descending number and you
will enter a deeper healthier level of mind ten nine feel going
going deeper, 8, 7, 6, deeper and deeper, 5, 4, 3, deeper
and deeper, 2, 1, you are We're now at a deeper, healthier
level of mind, deeper than before.
It is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed, a very healthy
state of being.
Effective Sensory Projection Statements for Success
I am now able to attune my intelligence by developing my sensing
faculties
and to experience myself as any point, place, level or depth so
as to be aware of any actions taking place.
I am able to function in non -locality regarding time and space.
I am aware that intelligence can exist at all levels and depths
in the universe and therefore I can attune to all information I
am now able to use my sensing faculties and to experience myself
as any matter as any any matter kingdom, mineral, plant, animal,
and human, if this is what I desire to do.
I am now able to detect abnormalities whenever such
abnormalities exist, within any kingdom, any level, and any
depth.
I am now able to apply corrective measures and to bring back
to normalcy any abnormality found within any kingdom any level
and any depth it's available at any level to be acted upon
to create through the subjective and objective dimensions we
will now program effective sensory projection for your success
and program information with the use of mental projection for
your benefit.
We will establish subjective points of reference in the
inanimate matter kingdom
at different levels and depths
for three objects that are similar and yet different.
In a moment, I am going to count from one to three
and cause a sound with my fingers.
At that time, You will project yourself mentally to the living
room in your home and imagine yourself standing in the center
facing the south wall.
1, 2, 3.
You are now standing in the center of your living room facing
the south wall.
At the count of 3, you will extend your arm objectively and
visualize the first object.
1, 2, 3.
Extend your arm objectively and visualize the first object.
Mentally, sense this object and relive and objectively repeat
all the movements made previously.
Examine this object from an external point of view.
Its color, size and shape, its texture and density.
Bring it closer and closer to your forehead.
mentally observe this object from a few inches away.
Now allow it to touch your forehead and mentally project
yourself into this object.
You are now within Within object number one, you may return your
hand to rest on your lap.
If you imagine the object to be just big enough for you
to fit in it, then you will not go very deeply inside.
But if you imagine the object as big as this room, then
you can go further within. if you will imagine this object to
be as large as a massive building and to feel your size
in contrast with it then you can go still further within using
the depth that this dimension of mind offers whenever you need
to increase the the illumination or amount or size of anything,
just snap the fingers of your right hand slightly
and expect the change to take place.
For a decrease or to return anything back to its original state,
snap the fingers of your left hand slightly
and expect the change to take place.
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as points of reference in the future at this
time we are going to subjectively conduct for test the The first
test will be for light, intensity, and color.
One, two, three.
Sense the intensity and color of light within this object number
one.
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three we will test for temperature one two three
since the the temperature within this object.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three,
we will test for odor. one two three sense the odor within
this object number one whatever you perceive with your
imagination at this dimension you can use as a point of
reference in the future at the count of three we will test
for solidity of material by knocking on the object one
two three objectively form a fist and go through the motions of
knocking on the object as you do do on a wall what
kind of sound do you subjectively hear how solid would you judge
the material to be whatever you perceive with your imagination
at this dimension you can use as a point of reference in
the future at the count of three you will objectively touch your
forehead one two three touch your forehead you're now coming out
of the object objectively extend your arm and and allow the
imaginary object to float in space by itself,
at a level a little higher than the horizontal plane or level
of sight.
You may return your hand to rest on your lap.
How does this object stand out against the natural color of the
wall?
keep the object rotating in your imagination keep it moving keep
it dynamic at the count of three the color of the wall
would change to red one two three the wall is now red
keep the object rotating noticing how it stands out against the
red background at the count of three the color of the wall
will change to green one two three the wall is now green
notice how the rotating object stands out against the green
background.
At the count of three the color of the wall will change
to blue. One, two, three.
The wall is now blue.
Notice how the rotating object stands out against the blue
background.
The color of the wall will now change back to green
back to red back to the actual color of the wall now
the object will disappear from the scene the object number one
has disappeared from the scene at the count of three we will
play back the impressions made with object number two.
One, two, three.
Extend your arm objectively and mentally play back the previous
impressions made with object number two.
Repeat every movement.
Bring your hand closer and closer as you As you observe the
color, the shape, the size, texture and density of object number
two.
Now touch your forehead and mentally project yourself into
object number two.
In your imagination, you are now within object number two, any
depth of this level you desire.
You may return your hand to rest on your lap.
Remember to use your finger snapping controls to increase and
decrease as necessary.
At the count of three, we will conduct the first test.
One, two, three.
Sense the intensity and color of light within object number two.
How does the light within object number two compare with that of
object number one?
What is the difference that makes the difference?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for temperature. One, two, three.
Sense the temperature within object number two.
How does the temperature of object number two compare with that
of object number one.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three test for For odor, one, two, three.
Sense the odor within object number two.
How does the odor of object number two compare with that of
object number one?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for solidity of material, one, two,
three. 3.
Objectively form a fist and knock on object number 2.
How does the imagined sound of object number 2 compare with that
of object number 1?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, touch your forehead to come out of
object number two. One, two, three.
Touch your forehead.
You are now coming out of object number two. 2.
Extend your arm and hold object number 2 at arm's length.
Now allow object number 2 to float in space using as a
background the natural color of your living room south wall.
Keep object number 2 rotating.
Keep it dynamic. you may return your hand to rest on your
lap at the count of three the color of the wall will
change to red one two three the wall is now red how
does object number two stand out against the red background how
does this compare with object number one keep object number two
rotating at the count of three the color of the wall will
change to green one two three the wall is now green how
does object number two stand out against a green background how
does this compare with object number one keep object number two
rotating at the count of three the color of the wall will
change to blue one two three the wall is now blue how
does object number two stand out against a blue background?
How does this compare to object number one?
Keep object number two rotating.
The color of the wall will now change back to green, back
to red, back to the actual color of the wall.
Now object number two will disappear from the scene.
object number two has disappeared from the scene at the count of
three we will visualize object number three one two three extend
your arm objectively and visualize object number three reliving
all of your previous movements as you bring your hand closer and
closer observe the color, the size and shape, the texture and
density
now touch your forehead and mentally project yourself into
object number three
you are now within object number three at any depth or level
you desire you may return your hand to rest on your lap
at the count of three we will conduct the first test one
two three 3.
Sense the intensity and color of light within object number 3.
How does the light within object number 3 compare with that of
object number 2 and object number 1?
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three tests for temperature one two three 3.
Sense the temperature within object number 3.
How does the temperature of object number 3 compare with that of
object number 2 and
and object number one.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, test for odor. one two three sense
the odor within object number three how does the odor of object
Object number three, compare with that of object number two, and
object number one.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future at
the count of three test for solidity of material one two three
objectively form a fist and knock on object number three how How
does a reflected sound of object number three compare with that
of object number two?
And object number one?
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as a point of reference in the future.
At the count of three, touch your forehead to come out of
object number three. One, two, three.
Touch your forehead.
You are now coming out of object number three.
Extend your arm and hold object number three at arm's length.
now allow object number three to float in space using as a
background the natural color of your living room south wall keep
object number three rotating keep it dynamic you may return your
hand to rest on your lap at the count of three the
color of the wall will change to red one two three the
wall is now red how does object number three stand out against
the red background.
How does this compare with object number two and object number
one.
Keep object number three rotating.
At the count of three the color of the wall will change
to green. One, two, three.
The wall is now green.
How does How does object number 3 stand out against a green
background?
How does this compare with object number 2?
And object number 1?
keep object number three rotating at the count of three the
color of the wall will change to blue one two three the
wall is now blue how does object number three stand out against
a blue background.
How does this compare with object number two and object number
one?
keep object number three rotating the color of the wall will now
change back to green back to red back to the actual color
of the wall now object number three will disappear from the
scene object number three has disappeared from the scene
whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension
you can use as points of reference in the future it is
now an accomplished fact that subjective points of reference
have been established at the inanimate matter Kingdom at at
different levels and different depths.
To function at these levels and to use these points of
reference,
all you need is to have a sincere desire to solve problems.
Your mind will automatically seek out these points of reference
where you will perceive
and become aware of information you can use to solve such
problems. and this is so every time you function at these levels
of the mind and at these points of reference you will receive
beneficial effects physically and mentally you may use these
levels of the mind in these points of reference to help yourself
to help your loved ones and to help any human being who
needs help physically and mentally you will always use these
levels of the mind in these points of reference in a
constructive creative manner for all that is good honest pure
clean and positive and this is so you will continue to strive
to take part in constructive and creative activities to make
this a better world to live in so that when you move
on you shall have You have left behind a better world for
those who follow.
You will consider the whole of humanity, depending on their
ages, as fathers or mothers, brothers or sisters, sons or
daughters.
You are a superior human being.
You have greater understanding, compassion, and patience with
others.
In a moment, I'm going to count from one to five and
cause a sound with my fingers. At that moment, you will open
your eyes, be wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect health,
feeling better than before.
1, 2, coming out slowly now, 3, at the count of 5
you will open your eyes, be wide awake, feeling fine and in
perfect health, feeling better than before. 4, 5,
eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect health,
feeling better than before.